adbureau.net 2002-12-02

# Engage, Inc. - Privacy On This Site

**What personally identifiable information is collected on this site?**  
Visitors may supply personally identifiable information (such as name, address or telephone numbers) for various purposes on this site. These purposes include registering to receive e-mail newsletters, requesting further information about our products, or simply asking a question about Engage. Engage does not collect personal information from you unless you provide it to us. This means that you can visit our site without telling us who you are or revealing any personally identifiable information about yourself. 

**How is it used?**  
When you supply information about yourself for a specific purpose, we use the information for only that purpose (such as to provide the service or information you have requested). For example, you may be asked to give us individual information to receive information, manage online services, or apply for a job. 

Should any material changes be made to the ways in which we use personally identifiable information, Engage will take commercially reasonable measures to obtain e-mail consent from you. We will also post the changes to our use of personally identifiable information on our site at least 30 days prior to a change. 

**Security**  
Personally identifiable information is stored on our Web server and is not publicly accessible. Further, personally identifiable information is only accessed by Engage employees on a "need to know" basis. All Engage employees must go through privacy training upon starting with Engage. Engage meets or exceeds all industry standards for the protection of personally identifiable information. 

**Choice/Opt-out**  
If you have registered to receive e-mail communications from us and later change your mind, you may contact us to have your name removed from our distribution lists. You have the following options to do this: 

You can send an e-mail to [privacy@engage.com](mailto:webmaster@engage.com?subject=Opt-out)

You can send mail to the following address: 

Corporate Counsel  
Engage, Inc.  
100 Brickstone Square  
Andover, MA 01810 

**Correct/Update**  
If you would like to verify the data we have received from you or to make corrections to it, you may contact us directly at the e-mail and mail addresses provided above. 

**What anonymous information is collected on this site?**  
Anonymous clickstream information is collected for every visitor to this site. This includes pages viewed, date and time, and browser type. IP numbers are not stored, but are temporarily used to determine domain type and in some cases, geographic region. We do not make any association between this information and a visitor's identity. 

**How is it used?**  
The information is used by Engage to build anonymous behavioral profiles, which are written to the Engage Knowledge® database -- securely housed at the Engage data center. These profiles are accessed by Engage-enabled Web sites to offer you personalized content and promotions, and to target relevant, more interesting ads -- all without knowing your identity. Again, there is no association between an Engage Knowledge profile and a visitor's identity. 

**How does this site use cookies?**  
Engage uses cookies to identify your browser as you visit pages on the Engage site or sites in the Engage media network. Cookies allow Engage to gather anonymous clickstream information. Cookies also allow Engage to provide more relevant, targeted advertising as you travel through sites in the Engage media network. 

For users who prefer not to have their Web usage information reflected in the Engage Knowledge database, Engage provides an opt-out procedure. 

**Links**  
This site may contain links to other Web sites. Please note that when you click on one of these links, you are entering another site. We encourage you to read the privacy statements of these linked sites as their privacy policy may differ from ours. 

**E-mail Links**  
We use e-mail links located on this site to allow you to contact us directly via e-mail. We use the information provided in your e-mail to respond to your questions or comments. We may also store your comments for future reference. Your personal information is only shared with third parties with your explicit permission. 

**Legal Disclaimer**  
We may disclose personal information when required by law or in the good-faith belief that such action is necessary in order to conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on Engage. 

**For more information**  
If you have any questions, concerns or comments, please e-mail [privacy@engage.com](mailto:privacy@engage.com).
